A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Building Inspection Office Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1898-1980
Library of Virginia
- 8 Family Apartment [9518 22nd Bay St.] and 16 Family Apartment [9512 22nd Bay St.] - Permit Number: 21476, 21477, 21478, Address: 9512, 9518 22nd Bay St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 19; Tag Number: 1970-130 (Box 56, Folder 853)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Piedmont Construction Corp.
- Consession Areas for Norfolk Outdoor Sports Complex - Permit Number: 21734, Address: Northampton Blvd. and Lake Wright, 1970, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-151 (Box 56, Folder 854)
  Drawn by: McElroy and Baldwin, Architects, 1600 East Little Creek Rd., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Commercial Builders, Inc.; Commissioned by: Harry M. Stevens
- [Sign for Virginia National Bank] - Permit Number: 22028, 22029, Address: TG-1 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-179 (Box 56, Folder 855)
  Drawn by: Talley Neon; Contractor: Talley Neon; Commissioned by: Virginia National Bank
- Addition and Alteration to United Air Lines Terminal and Air Freight Facilities, Norfolk Regional Airport Terminal Building - Permit Number: 21841, Address: Norfolk Regional Airport, 1970, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 22; Tag Number: 1970-165 (Box 56, Folder 856)
  Drawn by: Shriver and Holland Architects, Professional Arts Building, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Robert Morris Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Port and Industrial Authority
- Bell Telephone Building, 6th Floor Alterations - Permit Number: 20581, Address: 120 W. Bute St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-045 (Box 56, Folder 857)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: A. L. Ferguson, Inc.; Commissioned by: Bell Telephone Co.
- Masonry Building for John Copeland Motor Co. - Permit Number: 20505, Address: 4136 Granby St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-031 (Box 56, Folder 858)
  Drawn by: A. W. Tuttle, General Contractor, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: A. W. Tuttle; Commissioned by: Delia P. Bohannon
- [Alterations to Office Building] - Permit Number: 22136, Address: 324 W. 22nd St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-186 (Box 56, Folder 859)
  Drawn by: Elliott and Company, Inc., Norfolk, VA, Rocky Mount, NC; Contractor: Elliot and Co.; Commissioned by: Elliott and Co., Inc.
- [Alterations to] Surf and Ski, Store No. TH-4 - Permit Number: 22059, Address: TH-4 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-183 (Box 56, Folder 860)
  Drawn by: Bernard H. Lepselter, P. E., Consulting Engineers, 410 E. 62nd St., New York, NY; Commissioned by: Ashton H. Pully, Jr.
- [Alterations to] Modern Bridal, Store No. H-5 - Permit Number: 21624, Address: H-5 Military Cir., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-144 (Box 56, Folder 861)
  Drawn by: Bernard H. Lepselter, P. E., Consulting Engineers, 410 E. 62nd St., New York, NY; Contractor: Robert R. Marquis, Inc.; Commissioned by: Mrs. M. Wright
- One Story, 2 Bedroom Duplex - Permit Number: 69599, Address: 4001 Bluestone Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-077 (Box 56, Folder 862)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Man-Joe Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Judge William Shapiro
- [Alterations to] Checkered Flag Motor Car Co. - Permit Number: 69850, Address: 5636 E. Virginia Beach Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 11; Tag Number: 1980-096 (Box 56, Folder 863)
  Drawn by: Evan J. McCorkle, Jr., A.I.A. and Associates, Architects and Planning Consultants, Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Checkered Flag
- [New Office and Shop Facility for J. W. Burress, Inc.] - Permit Number: 69666, Address: 5730 Sellger Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 15; Tag Number: 1980-082 (Box 56, Folder 864)
  Drawn by: Baldwin and Gregg, Engineers - Surveyors - Planners, Norfolk - Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: J. W. Burress
- Residence for Ms. Peggy Jensen, Ghent Square - Permit Number: 73701, Address: 352 W. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1980-352 (Box 56, Folder 865)
  Drawn by: Verebely and Associates, Architects, Suite 32, 809 Live Oak Dr., Chesapeake, VA; Contractor: George Jensen, Inc.; Commissioned by: Peggy Jensen
- Barge Receiving and Shiploading Modification, Continental Grain Co. - Permit Number: 68935, 68936, Address: 8701 Hampton Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-003 (Box 56, Folder 866)
  Drawn by: R. S. Fling and Partners, Inc., Consulting Engineers, 999 Crupper Ave., Columbus, OH; Contractor: Tidewater Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Continental Grain Co.
- Marquis Villa Townhouses - Permit Number: 79585-73596, Address: 8534, 8538, 8542, 8546, 8550, 8554 Chesapeake Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1980-412 (Box 56, Folder 867)
  Drawn by: Harold O. Warner and Associates, Architects, Suite 201, 124 S. Lynnhaven Rd., Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: Virginia Realty Co.; Commissioned by: W. F. Thornton, Jr.; Notes: Permit # 73591-73596 are for fences at these addresses.
- K. and T. Weller's Duplex - Permit Number: 73915, Address: 4504 Perch Ln., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-424 (Box 56, Folder 868)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Kevin Weller
- Reynolds [Residence] Rehab[ilitation] - Permit Number: 73576, Address: 1412 Ashland Cir., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-410 (Box 57, Folder 869)
  Drawn by: Thad A. Broom; Commissioned by: Evelyn and Richard Reynolds
- Residence of Mrs. Mills W. Darden, Jr., Algonquin Park - Permit Number: 74016, Address: 1360 North Shore Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1980-434 (Box 57, Folder 870)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Mrs. Mills Darden, Jr.
- C and P Telephone Offices, Circle East Building - Permit Number: 69120, Address: 861 Glenrock Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-024 (Box 57, Folder 871)
  Drawn by: Morrisette, Cederquist, Bondurant and Associates, Architects, Engineers, Planners; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Co.
- [New Warehouse Building and Office Addition for David P. Jacobson and Co., Inc.] - Permit Number: 73856, 73857, Address: 1349 Engleside Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 16; Tag Number: 1980-421 (Box 57, Folder 872)
  Drawn by: Maxwell B. Edwards, P. E., Consulting Engineer, Civil, Structural, Norfolk, VA; Brundage, Cohen, and Holton, A.I.A., Architects, Suite 523-527, Law Building, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: David P. Jacobson Co., Inc.
- Office and Shop Building, Creative Displays, Inc. - Permit Number: 68951, Address: 5547 E. Virginia Beach Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 14; Tag Number: 1980-007 (Box 57, Folder 873)
  Drawn by: Randall A. Strawbridge, incorporated, Consulting Engineers, Richmond, VA; Contractor: Gresham Metal Buildings Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Creative Displays, Inc.
- Braywood Manor, Phase II, Proposed Store and Offices - Permit Number: 69597, Address: 7010 Auburn Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1980-075 (Box 57, Folder 874)
  Drawn by: Adkins and Associates, Consulting Engineers, Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: Braywood Manor Associates
- [1 Family Residences,] Ghent Commons - Permit Number: 73870-73879, Address: 201, 209, 217, 225 Shirley Ave.; 1417, 1425, 1433 Queens Way; 1400, 1408, 1416 Llewellyn Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 32; Tag Number: 1980-423 (Box 57, Folder 875)
  Drawn by: Cohen and Haft, Holtz Kerxton and Assoicates, Architects and Planners; Commissioned by: Christopher Development Co.
- Townhouses for William E. Wood - Permit Number: 68928-68933, Address: 1110, 1112, 1114 Llewellyn Mews, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 11; Tag Number: 1980-001 (Box 57, Folder 876)
  Drawn by: Morrisette, Cederquist, Bondurant and Associates, Architects, Engineers, Planners; Contractor: O'Brien Construction Co.; Commissioned by: B. A. W. Corp.
- Downtown Raquet Club - Permit Number: 69635, Address: 326 Granby St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-080 (Box 57, Folder 877)
  Drawn by: WGP Architects, A.I.A., P. O. Box 1791, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Roladine Corp.
- Alterations and Additions to Existing Warehouse [for] New Research Laboratory, ODU Research Foundation of Old Dominion University - Permit Number: 69111, Address: 1037 W. 46th St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1980-022 (Box 57, Folder 878)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: C. F. Hardy Building Corp.; Commissioned by: Sidney Finkelstein
- Residence, 3 Bedroom, for Tides Realty - Permit Number: 68942, Address: 195 W. Lorengo Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-004 (Box 57, Folder 879)
  Drawn by: H. R. Schippell, Certified Professional Engineer, 3232 Verdun Ave, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Tides Realty
- Best Repair Company, Renovations to Existing Areas in Main Building - Permit Number: 68993, Address: 2406 DeBree Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1980-011 (Box 57, Folder 880)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Best Repair Co., Inc.
- Addition to Existing Building for Walker and Laberge Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 69154, Address: 7613 Sewells Point Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-028 (Box 57, Folder 881)
  Drawn by: Alfred E. Abiouness; Commissioned by: Walker and Laberge Co. Inc.
- Barge Receiving and Shiploading Modification, Continental Grain Co. - Permit Number: 68934, Address: 8701 Hampton Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1980-002 (Box 57, Folder 882)
- [Warehouse for] Hall Hodges Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 69843, Address: 1344 Ballentine Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-095 (Box 57, Folder 883)
  Drawn by: R. D. Lambert and Son, Inc.; Contractor: R. D. Lambert and Son, Inc.; Commissioned by: Hall Hodges Co., Inc.
- Four Unit Apartment Building - Permit Number: 69023, Address: 589 W. Ocean View Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-012 (Box 57, Folder 884)
  Drawn by: Edwin B. Small, Architect-Engineer; Commissioned by: Billyn Woods
- [Signs for Pantry Pride Store No. 76] - Permit Number: 69582, 69583, 69584, Address: 201 E. Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-074 (Box 57, Folder 885)
  Drawn by: Peninsular Sign Co., St. Petersburg, FL; Contractor: Calhoun Sign Co.; Commissioned by: Pantry Pride
- [Alterations and Additions to] 418 Warren Crescent - Permit Number: 69040, Address: 418 Warren Cres., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-015 (Box 57, Folder 886)
  Drawn by: Rancorn Wildman Krause, A.I.A., Architects Planners, Suite 230, 229 Bute St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Snyder Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: B. F. Hartwig
- Kitchen and Social Hall Alterations at Talbot Park Baptist Church - Permit Number: 69825, Address: 6919 Granby St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-094 (Box 57, Folder 887)
  Drawn by: A. Ray Pentecost, Jr., and Associates, Inc., Architects, 7460 Tidewater Dr., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: Talbot Park Baptist Church
- [Alterations to] Shulman's, Inc. - Permit Number: 69744, Address: Bldg. H Military Cir., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 17; Tag Number: 1980-088 (Box 58, Folder 888)
  Drawn by: Kussa/Trauth, Ltd., 150 N. Wacker Dr., Chicago, IL; Contractor: C. F. Hardy Building Corp.; Commissioned by: Shulman's, Inc.
- C and P Telephone Building - Permit Number: 69751, 69572, Address: 9559 15th Bay St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-073 (Box 58, Folder 889)
  Drawn by: Oliver, Smith and Cook, Ltd., Architects-Planners, Norfolk and Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: G. L. Cline and Son, Inc.; Commissioned by: Chesapeak and Potomac Telephone Co.
- [Alterations and Additions to] Downtown Racquet Club, Inc. - Permit Number: 69037, Address: 324 Granby St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 35; Tag Number: 1980-014 (Box 58, Folder 890)
  Drawn by: WGP Architects, A.I.A., P. O. Box 1791, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Charles A. Wright and Assoc.; Commissioned by: Downtown Racquet Club, Inc.
- Crockford Residence, Botetourt Gardens - Permit Number: 69207, Address: 1320 Botetourt Gardens, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 14; Tag Number: 1980-035 (Box 58, Folder 891)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Jennifer Crockford
- Lawrence Residence, Ocean View - Permit Number: 73931, Address: 1122 Toler Pl., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1980-427 (Box 58, Folder 892)
  Drawn by: The Design Collaborative, Principal, Laxzlo Aranyi, A.I.A., 138 Rosemont Rd., Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: Gregory Kent Lawrence
- Branch Office for Life Federal Savings and Loan Assoc., Roosevelt Gardens Shopping Center - Permit Number: 69050, Address: 2336 E. Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-016 (Box 58, Folder 893)
  Drawn by: Gary W. Bright, Architect, A.I.A., 2466 Pleasure House Rd., Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: C. F. Hardy Building Corp.; Commissioned by: Life Federal Savings and Loan Co.
- Ne w Addition for Bauer Compressor - Permit Number: 68967, Address: 1328 Azalea Garden Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 19; Tag Number: 1980-009 (Box 58, Folder 894)
  Drawn by: Harold O. Warner and Associates, Architects, Suite 201, 124 S. Lynnhaven Rd., Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: Bauer Compressor, Inc.
- Storage Shed for Arthur Polizos Residence - Permit Number: 73733, 73734, Address: 1221 Gates Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-418 (Box 58, Folder 895)
  Drawn by: Williams and Tazewell and Associates, Inc., Architects Planners, A.I.A., 710 W. 21st St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: M. D. Johnson and Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Arthur Polizos
- [Duplex] - Permit Number: 74015, Address: 2301 Hemlock St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-433 (Box 58, Folder 896)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Wayne C. Lusk
- [New Addition to Storage Building and Office, Norfolk Junk Co.] - Permit Number: 69598, Address: 1100 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-076 (Box 58, Folder 897)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Hardison Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Junk Co.
- Addition to Norfolk Flowershop Located at Roosevelt Gardens - Permit Number: 73644, Address: 2320 W. Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-413 (Box 58, Folder 898)
  Drawn by: Spigel, Herman, Chapman, Architects and Engineers, 420 W. Bute St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: George Jensen; Commissioned by: Norfolk Flower Shop
- Cornwopper Restaurant Addition - Permit Number: 69880, Address: 3930 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-098 (Box 58, Folder 899)
  Drawn by: H. R. Schippell, Certified Professional Engineer, 3232 Verdun Ave, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Roosevelt Hatch
- [Picnic Shelter, Ocean View Golf Course] - Permit Number: 69808, Address: S.E. of 116 Battersea Rd., 1980, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-093 (Box 58, Folder 900)
  Drawn by: City of Norfolk, Dept. of Parks and Recreation; Commissioned by: City of Norfolk
- [Addition to Store] - Permit Number: 69190, Address: 3026 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-030 (Box 58, Folder 901)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: T. E. Morgan and Co., Inc.
- [Interior Alterations to] Big Tony's Pizza and Subs for Jonas, Inc. - Permit Number: 69796, Address: 3200 Tidewater Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-091 (Box 58, Folder 902)
  Drawn by: H. R. Schippell, Certified Professional Engineer, 3232 Verdun Ave, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Anthony S. Porter
- Personnel Relocation in Headquarters Building, Virginia National Bank - Permit Number: 68944, Address: 315 E. Main St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-005 (Box 58, Folder 903)
  Drawn by: Williams and Tazewell and Associates, Architects, A.I.A., 710 W. 21st St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Virginia National Bank
- Rental Storage Units for U-Haul of Tidewater Virginia - Permit Number: 69772, 69773, Address: 5609 Raby Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-089 (Box 58, Folder 904)
  Drawn by: Benjamin B. Adderholdt, Jr., A.I.A., Architect, 436 Court St., Portsmouth, VA; Contractor: Richard Dobson Building, Inc.; Commissioned by: U-Haul Co. of VA
- [1 Family Residence with Attached Garage] - Permit Number: 69121, Address: 2439 Rush St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-25 (Box 58, Folder 905)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Tommy Mustin Plastering Co.; Commissioned by: Tommy Mustin
- [2 Family Residence] - Permit Number: 68965, Address: 4221 Dunning Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-008 (Box 58, Folder 906)
  Drawn by: P. Lara; Contractor: Michael Builders, Inc.; Commissioned by: George M. Edwards
- [Deck and Garage Addition] - Permit Number: 69549, Address: 401 Brickley Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-071 (Box 58, Folder 907)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Toren Adams Building Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Steve Peppas
- 1 Family Residence - Permit Number: 69678, Address: 6110 Hampton Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-084 (Box 58, Folder 908)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Godfrey Brothers, Inc.
- Addition to Berkely Machine Works and Foundry Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 69791, Address: 819 Pearl St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-090 (Box 58, Folder 909)
  Drawn by: R. D. Lambert and Son, Inc.; Contractor: R. D. Lambert and Son, Inc.; Commissioned by: Berkley Machine Works
- [Alterations to Furniture Store] - Permit Number: 69099, Address: 500 Granby St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-021 (Box 58, Folder 910)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Carpenters Unlimited; Commissioned by: Crockin Levy Co.
- Proposed Covered Storage Shed - Permit Number: 69210, Address: 2631 Arkansas Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-036 (Box 59, Folder 911)
  Drawn by: Edwin B. Small, Architect-Engineer; Contractor: J. E. Weddle and Assoc., Inc.; Commissioned by: J. E. Weddle and Associates, Inc.
- Southgate Terminals, Norfolk Industiral Park - Permit Number: 69085, 69086, 72949, Address: 1400 and 1404 Sewells Point Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 41; Tag Number: 1980-019 (Box 59, Folder 912)
  Drawn by: Leavitt Associates, Architects and Engineers, 4400 Colley Ave., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Southgate Terminals
- Alterations and Additions, Phase 2, DePaul Hospital - Permit Number: 73951, Address: 150 Kingsley Ln., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-429 (Box 59, Folder 913)
  Drawn by: Baskervill and Son, Architects and Engineers, 2313 W. Cary St., Richmond, VA; Contractor: W. B. Meredith, II, Inc.; Commissioned by: DePaul Hospital
- [Addition to Sheet Metal Shop] - Permit Number: 69126, Address: E. End of Rose St., 1980, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-026 (Box 59, Folder 914)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co.
- United Virginia Bank, Bache-Halsey-Stuart-Shields - Permit Number: 73694, Address: 5 Main Plaza East, 1980, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-416 (Box 59, Folder 915)
  Drawn by: McGaughy, Marshall, and McMillan, Architects and Consulting Engineers, Norfolk, VA; Washington, DC; Athens, Greece; Houston, TX; Contractor: Conrad Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: United Bank of Virginia
- Bethel Baptist Church, Educational Building Annex and Nave Renovations - Permit Number: 74018, Address: 1234 Reservoir Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 13; Tag Number: 1980-435 (Box 59, Folder 916)
  Drawn by: Livas and Associates, Architects, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Urlson U. Hill; Commissioned by: Bethel Baptist Church
- Added Dimensions-LaVogue, Military Circle Shoppes - Permit Number: 69112, Address: 700 N. Military Cir., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-023 (Box 59, Folder 917)
  Drawn by: Morrisette, Cederquist, Bondurant and Associates, Architects, Engineers, Planners; Contractor: C. F. Hardy Building Corp.; Commissioned by: Equitable Life
- [Renovation to] Leggett, Military Circle - Permit Number: 69798, Address: Bldg. D Military Cir., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1980-092 (Box 59, Folder 918)
  Drawn by: Surratt, Smith and Abernathy Associates, Architects, Charlotte, NC; Contractor: Suitt Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Leggett's Department Store
- School of Nursing (Kingsley Lane Apartments) - Permit Number: 69200, Address: 103 Kingsley Ln., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 26; Tag Number: 1980-034 (Box 59, Folder 919)
  Drawn by: Baskervill and Son, Architects and Engineers, 2313 W. Cary St., Richmond, VA; Contractor: Conrad Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: DePaul Hospital
- Arthur Real Estate Corporation, Warehouse No. 2, Norfolk Industrial Park - Permit Number: 69707, Address: 1360 Ingleside Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 14; Tag Number: 1980-087 (Box 59, Folder 920)
  Drawn by: Shriver and Holland Associates, Architects-Planners-Project Coordinators, 355 W. Freemason St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: George Jensen, Inc.; Commissioned by: Arthur Real Estate Corp.
- Beach Residence - Permit Number: 69681, Address: 951 Little Bay Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-085 (Box 59, Folder 921)
  Drawn by: Resort Custom Builders; Contractor: Resort Custom Construction Co.; Commissioned by: William H. Norris
- Three Bedroom Ranch - Permit Number: 69093, Address: 321 Curtis St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-020 (Box 59, Folder 922)
  Drawn by: F and W Construciton Co.; Contractor: F and W Construction Co.; Commissioned by: F and W Construction Co.
- Two Bedroom Duplex - Permit Number: 69197, Address: 1200 Hillside Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-031 (Box 59, Folder 923)
  Drawn by: Nestor Construction Co.; Contractor: Nestor Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Nestor Construction Co.
- A Single Family Residence For Tides Realty Co. - Permit Number: 69199, Address: 3312 Verdun Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-033 (Box 59, Folder 924)
  Drawn by: George S[?]; Commissioned by: Tides Realty
- [Duplex] - Permit Number: 69033, 69070, Address: 815, 819 W. 47th St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-013, 1980-017 (Box 59, Folder 925)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Otis D. Winn; Commissioned by: Steve Loder
- [Alterations to] Live Oak Sound, Inc. - Permit Number: 73916, Address: 110 College Pl., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1980-425 (Box 59, Folder 926)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: K and W Enterprises; Commissioned by: Live Oak Sound, Inc.
- Tahoe II [Two Story, Single Family Residence] - Permit Number: 73999, Address: 6135 Powhatan Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 17; Tag Number: 1980-432 (Box 59, Folder 927)
  Drawn by: Kingsberry Homes, Boise Cascade Corporation; Contractor: Beam Development Corp.; Commissioned by: Frank K. Tarrant
- Proposed Six Unit Townhouse - Permit Number: 73933, Address: 1252 W. Ocean View Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-428 (Box 60, Folder 928)
  Drawn by: Woodsmen Builders, Inc.; Commissioned by: Billy M. Woods